Fear not the weapon, but the hand that wields it.
Ninja Assassin is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by James McTeigue.
Ninja Assassin follows Raizo, one of the deadliest assassins in the world.
Taken from the streets as a child, he was transformed into a trained killer by the
Ozunu Clan, a secret society whose very existence is considered a myth.
But haunted by the merciless execution of his friend by the
Clan, Raizo breaks free from them and vanishes.
Now he waits, preparing to exact his revenge.
Raizo, played by Rain.
Mika, played by Naomie Harris.
Maslow, played by Ben Miles.
Takeshi, played by Rick Yune.
Ozunu, played by Sho Kosugi.
Tattoo Master, played by Randall Duk Kim.
Ninja Assassin is a 2009 neo-noir martial arts film directed by James
McTeigue, from a screenplay by Matthew Sand and J.
Michael Straczynski.
It stars Rain as a disillusioned assassin from a modern-day ninja clan, looking
for retribution against his former mentor, played by Sho Kosugi.
The cast also features Naomie Harris, Ben Miles, and Rick Yune.
The film was produced by The Wachowskis, Joel Silver and Grant Hill under
Legendary Pictures, Dark Castle Entertainment and Silver Pictures.
It was distributed by Warner Bros.
Pictures, and premiered in theaters across the
United States on November 25, 2009.
It received generally negative reviews from critics,
but was a moderate commercial success.
The film explores themes of martial arts, assassin,
assassination, ninja fighter, gore.
The tone is intense.